JONGHWA NOH

WebDeveloper

📞 +821075577177 @ nicenoz@gmail.com 🕜 linkedin.com/in/jonga

Seoul, Korea

SUMMARY

I have experienced various technologies through various development environments in various platform and provided quality services with various frameworks. In the future, I will actively use the skills I have acquired to contribute to the development of the company. And if there are some skills to grow our company, I'll spare no effort learning new things. As a junior developer, I worked for 6+ years at fields such as in korea famous company POSCO, SKT, LOTTE CINEMA, and startup delivery company as backend developer. I made IOT program, internal community system, MES(manufacturing Excution System), and delivery system by using dotnet framework(Winform, Web App) and javascript. Also, As a senior developer, I worked for a year at LG Energy Solution. There, I have made MES Web App as a full stack developer by using React, Spring framework, Oracle, Elastic search.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer at LG EnergySolution

01/2022 - Ongoing

LG Energy Solution

Seoul, Korea

- Full Stack Developed, such as Front(React), Back End(Spring), SQL(Oracle)
- · Using High-Chart Framework, and Wijmo Framework.
- · Using Query in Oracle and Elasticsearch.
- · Worked as Full Time freelancer.
- Work for Image Processing and Binding a MES Data.

Junior Software Developer

2014 - 2021

Various Sites

Seoul, Korea

- worked mostly as Back-end developer.
- At first, In MES site I starting developing Windows Form application.
- And then, I have developed for Delivery Service in Korea
- I have experienced at Back-End such as nodejs, ASP.NET
- Also I have experienced DBMS, MySQL(MariaDB), SQL-SERVER, Oracle, No-SQL(redis, MongoDB, ElasticSearch)
- I have interest at DevOps, such as CICD, K8s, Docker and Google Analytics.
- Also I have experienced cloud AWS, and Azure.

EDUCATION

BS in Electronics and Communications Engineering

03/2009 - 01/2014

Kwangwoon University

Seoul, Korea

Since childhood, I have loved the practice environment. I majored in computer science in high school, but I did not get good grades in theoretical subjects such as Korean, English, and mathematics. However, I was interested in computer science-related practical courses, which led to good grades. When my classmates struggled and lagged behind, I taught them where they got stuck. I came to know that I can help someone and that there are subjects where I can do better than my friends, and that experience helped me decide on my career path in college.

When I was in college, I felt that I couldn't just practice well in programming. The theory developed through practice had limitations, and I expanded the theory through information searching. There was a lot of good information, but there was also a lot of wrong information, so I tried to understand the principle by repeatedly testing it, finding the most suitable case among them, and applying it. Thanks to my efforts at that time, I am now a developer who can experience and handle various frameworks on various platforms.

License

1. Engineer Information Processing

Seoul, Korea

2. Driver's license



ACHIEVEMENTS

Develop MES as FullStack Eng

Develop MES from BackEnd to FrontEnd as a senior WebDeveloper in about 10-people team

20% improved JavaScript Performance

by using react dev tools, memorize a resource.

SKILLS

Language/FrameWork

C · Java · C# · JavaScript · Html5 ·

Verilog[HDL] · DotNetCore · Spring ·

 ${\sf NodeJS} \cdot {\sf React} \cdot {\sf Vue} \cdot {\sf WebRTC} \cdot {\sf JQuery} \cdot \\$

BootStrap

SOL

Oracle \cdot MS-SQL \cdot DB2 \cdot My-sql(MariaDB) \cdot

MongoDB · ElasticSearch · Redis

DevOps/Tools

Git · SVN · SourceSAFE · Harvest · TFS ·

K8s · Docker · Jenkins · WinCC ·

GoogleAnalytics

Operating Systems/Cloud

Windows · Linux(RHEL/CentOS/Ubuntu) ·

MacOS · AWS · Azure

STRENGTHS

★ Various Experience

Having various experience at many sites.
Being confident of completing my work successfully.

work successfully. Having tireless effort

★ Tireless Effort

Having a lot of experience of successful completion and confidence to finish. Like to enjoy new experiences and learn to new things.

INTERESTS

DevOps, Docker, K8s, WebRTC